Support Admin Watch on
kissasia.cam or kisskh.org
♪The moon rests on the treetops,
listening to the evening breeze♪
♪Wine in hand,
I sing as stars shine in disarray♪
♪The endless night
keeps but one lonely lamp♪
♪Who knows if I'm warm or cold♪
♪Years of companionship
vanish like mist♪
♪How many roads must a deep love travel♪
♪The returned soul
wears robes of regret♪
♪Brushing off dust with a wave♪
♪Wind or no wind, I think of you♪
♪Beyond words♪
♪A vow is cherished all the time♪
♪Some souls yearn to ferment time♪
♪Into a story♪
♪Crushing the past,
I let old memories fade♪
♪Don't let this story end♪
=Beyond The Loop=
=Episode 3=
He loves me.
He doesn't love me.
So be it.
Wait.
My lady.
What are you doing here?
I brought you wine.
- You two, put the wine over there.
- Yes.
Premium osmanthus wine. Try it.
(I vaguely remember basking
in his affection in my dreams.)
(Only then could I drink freely.)
Wan.
What are you doing?
I'm planting flowers.
Why did you buy so much wine?
Because I know you enjoy drinking.
From today onward,
I will never drink another drop of wine.
Who is your inside informant?
Do you think I can't find out
just because you won't tell me?
Go ahead and investigate.
Even if I die,
I'll never tell you
who the informant is.
Wei Feng, release him.
My lord, we finally caught one.
Releasing him will waste our efforts.
I said it. Release him.
If your accomplices
see you safely released,
what fate awaits you?
You should know better than I do.
You...
Still not telling me?
I only seek
to die honorably for Mobei.
Wei Feng, watch him.
Throw him out in a few days.
Yes.
Mu Yunqing!
Just kill me!
Will you really throw the assassin out?
No more interrogations?
Look at him.
Does he look like
he'll give us anything?
Those Mobei assassins were too bold.
Attempting to kill you
on your wedding day.
An inside job.
They're overreaching.
The Madam was investigating
before the assassins came.
Could she know something?
Watch Liu Bingmo closely.
Find out what they're really planning.
Yes.
Things are getting tense.
Every city has those coveting my token.
We must plan ahead.
What do you plan to do?
Spread the word
that the assassin has confessed
and will be released soon.
Yes.
I'll make them know
Jin City is not theirs to touch.
Neither is the Central Plains.
Who?
Let's go.
(Shili Pavilion)
Mr. Song, drink with us.
Madam Hong let us teach you how to talk
(Song Qiming, Madam Hong's son)
to girls.
Don't be shy now.
Lady,
maintain boundaries.
Please show restraint.
Mr. Song.
- Okay.
- This is your home.
Take it easy.
Drink up.
Sir, drink.
Go on, drink.
I really can't drink anymore, ladies.
Miss.
(Why do I feel so close to this lady)
(the first time we meet?)
You were so shy earlier,
but now, you're embracing another girl.
- I...
- Mr. Song.
Seems you don't need any teaching.
Let's go.
S-S-Safe travels.
Ladies,
next time my mother summons you,
please don't come!
Miss.
Yu Yingwan.
Sir,
the woman beside you is my wife.
I'm taking her back now.
Wait! Stop!
How can you prove she's your wife?
Look, I got it.
Brilliant.
Wan, are you alright?
You're bleeding.
There's a wound on her neck.
You are lying.
Her neck bears no scar whatsoever.
(How could this be?)
(Could it be...?)
That man abandoned
her here without explanation.
What if you want to harm her?
What if that man was trying to save her?
If I give her to you,
wouldn't I be an accomplice?
How about this?
When this young lady
awakens tomorrow morning,
I'll escort her
wherever she wants to go.
You may leave now.
No.
My lord, this is the Shili Pavilion.
Madam Hong is renowned for her virtue.
Moreover, the mansion
isn't secure tonight.
Let's return
and let the Madam sleep here peacefully.
We'll come get her tomorrow.
Mr. Song.
I know your family
is a prominent merchant family.
You're a gentleman.
I trust you will
take good care of my wife tonight.
We shall take our leave now.
If any harm befalls my wife,
you know the consequences.
Miss.
What is this?
(Keep Miss Yu at your mansion.)
Found the poisoning source?
The autopsy is pending.
We'll report to you immediately.
Red sores.
I've never seen this type of poison.
Everyone who entered the prison today
has been questioned.
No irregularities.
Identify this poison without fail.
My lord.
This must be the work of that Mobei spy.
Shall we dig deeper?
It was done so secretly.
The perpetrator knows my mansion well.
They're hidden,
but we're exposed.
Don't alert the enemy.
But we can't stay idle.
Look into the Yunluo Incense
and then the mole.
Yes.
(Shili Pavilion)
Who are you?
Did you sleep well?
♪Winter snow waltzes
before the courtyard♪
♪Palaces show no mercy♪
♪So much courage it takes♪
♪To retrace each step♪
♪Memory's whispers, dreams or illusion♪
♪Butterflies climb mountains for love♪
♪Perish before the flowers♪
♪You seem so distant,
yet right before my eyes♪
♪A game of chess, a fate of strife♪
♪I dream of standing
with you, side by side♪
♪If you would meet me face to face♪
♪I'd die without a single regret♪
♪You're the untouchable star♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪Through all the tides of love and hate♪
♪Our eyes met across the mortal world♪
♪When breezes stirred by my window♪
♪Cherry blossoms rained in the sky♪
♪You're the distant star♪
♪I'm the tiniest speck♪
♪Spend all my devotion♪
♪For your tears and embrace♪
♪I'll brave all the blizzards♪
♪To walk with you♪